Guide to the National Education Association-Councils records, 1849-1983 NEA1004.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- National Council on Teacher Retirement, 1926-1974; series 6; 2.5 Linear Feet
  - Report of the Committee of One Hundred on Retirement Allowances, July 1933; series 6 (Box 4325, Folder 4)
  - Report of the Committee on Retirement Allowance, 1928-1932; series 6 (Box 4325, Folder 5)
  - Report of the NEA Special Committee on Teacher Retirement; Reprinted from "Reports of Committees Presented to the 57th Representative Assembly 1978", ca. 1978; series 6 (Box 4325, Folder 6)
  - Retirement Information Series Memorandum, March 1973; series 6 (Box 4325, Folder 7)
  - Retirement Systems in the Depression: Report of the Committee on Retirement Allowances, ca. 1934; series 6 (Box 4325, Folder 8)
  - School Law Summaries: Retirement [file 1/2], 1963-1967; series 6 (Box 4325, Folder 9)
  - School Law Summaries: Retirement [file 2/2], 1963-1967; series 6 (Box 4325, Folder 10)
  - Statistics of Teacher Retirment Systems 1946-1947, 1949-50, 1950-51, 1951-52, 1952-53, 1948 - 1954; series 6 (Box 4326, Folder 1)
  - Statutory Analysis of Retirement Provisions for Teachers and Other School Employees, 1942 - 1944; series 6 (Box 4326, Folder 2)
  - Statutory Provisions for Statewide Retirement Systems, 1946-1948; seies 6 (Box 4326, Folder 3)
  - Teacher Retirement Systems: A Summary of the 1971 Legal Provisions for Retirement Systems to Which Teachers Belong, 1972; series 6 (Box 4326, Folder 4)
  - Teacher Retirement Systems: A Summary of the 1973 Legal Provisions for Retirement Systems to Which Teachers Belong, 1974; series 6 (Box 4326, Folder 5)
  - Teacher Retirement Systems: A Summary of the 1975 Legal Provisions for Retirement Systems to Which Teachers Belong, 1976; series 6 (Box 4326, Folder 6)
  - Teachers' Pensions: Report of the Committee on Pensions, July 1923; series 6 (Box 4326, Folder 7)
  - Teachers' Retirement Allowances: Report of the Committee on the Problem of Retirement Allowances, July 1924, 1926; series 6 (Box 4326, Folder 8)
  - Teachers' Salaries and Cost of Living, July 1918; series 6 (Box 4326, Folder 9)